<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>places on estebanvalencia.com</title>
    <link>/tags/places/</link>
    <description>Recent content in places on estebanvalencia.com</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/places/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Stellisee - Zermatt, Valais</title>
      <link>/photos/stellisee/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/photos/stellisee/</guid>
      <description>Brief Overview Stellisee is a mountain lake in Zermatt, Valais with a clear reflection of the Matterhorn as the lake is a very desired photo op spot.
A few kilometer hike away from Zermatt, this slice of serenity offers more than a good location for photography; it offers peace, tranquility and warmth in November along a beautiful trail traversing glaciers. Although that might not seem like a substantial trail, consider the a 15 - 20% all along the way to the final destination.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Charlotte, North Carolina</title>
      <link>/photos/charlotte-nc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/photos/charlotte-nc/</guid>
      <description>Charlotte&amp;rsquo;s got a lot of great things to do.
Charlotte Charlotte is a gorgeous small city deep into North Carolina with big green banks, both financially and environmentally. Charlotte left a lasting impact on me due to the relaxing ambience of a green and modern city.
Cool things about Charlotte:  No zoo animals in captivity - they consent to paying rent 150,000 square foot NASCAR Hall of Fame gives way to easy streets Mint Museum in a banking city capital to see the origins of cash Underwhelming skyscrapers to let you enjoy the sunrise and sunset  My time I have spent time travelling to Charlotte for work and pleasure in the past.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scarborough Bluffs - Toronto, ON</title>
      <link>/photos/toronto-on-i/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/photos/toronto-on-i/</guid>
      <description>The Scarborough Bluffs is a steep-sided escarpment along the ridge of Lake Ontario in Toronto, Ontario, Canada. Measuring roughly 15km in length reaching 90m above the coast line, what is left is a dangerously beautiful clay cliff traversing a series of beautiful parks overlooking the lake with a few spots to access your boat.
Spots to checkout Bluffer&amp;rsquo;s Park is definitely a must see, but specifically there are such beautiful parts to the area that exploring it is mildly rewarding to find a small oasis along the coast line.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cheery Beach/Tommy Thompson/Leslie Street Split - Toronto, ON</title>
      <link>/photos/toronto-on-ii/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/photos/toronto-on-ii/</guid>
      <description>Brief Overview Leslie Street Split is certainly not a name I have ever referred to it as.
It also seems like I am not the only one:
 Its common name is technically incorrect, since it is not truly a spit, but Torontonians almost never use the official name. The road running along the peninsula is a southern extension of Leslie Street, hence the popular nickname.
  Same Wikipedia as above  A mild environmental retreat amidst the concrete jungle given that Toronto Region Conservation Authority actively manages this Environmentally Sensitivie Area as a result of having an important bird population.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
