<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>It Happened on estebanvalencia.com</title>
    <link>/photos/</link>
    <description>Recent content in It Happened on estebanvalencia.com</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 09 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/photos/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>China&#39;s Great Leap Forward</title>
      <link>/photos/great-leap-forward-i/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/photos/great-leap-forward-i/</guid>
      <description>TL;DR: The Chinese population is declining and there are several compounding issues such as limited farmland and an overweight retiring demographic forcing China to be creative to sustain their aggressive growth distributed among fewer working heads.
China faces a quadruple bind: China’s margin of error starts razor thin, and not only because its lands are below subpar. One downside of China’s massive population is that the country has less farmland per person than Saudi Arabia.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Paninis</title>
      <link>/photos/grub-love-ii/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/photos/grub-love-ii/</guid>
      <description>The first U.S. reference to panini dates to 1956 and a precursor appeared in a 16th-century Italian cookbook. Panini sandwiches became trendy in Milanese bars, called paninoteche as a quick lunch choice for office workers in the 1970s. New York has adapted the panini by selling the sandwiches with distinctive variations.
Classic fillings in Italy:
 mozzarella, tomato (plus arugula and/or prosciutto); prosciutto and fontina cheese prosciutto, chese and olive tapenade; bresaola, goat cheese or stracchino (plus lettuce and/or tomato); speck (smoked cured prosciutto from Tyrol), arugula and cheese grilled vegetables and cheese.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Charlotte, North Carolina</title>
      <link>/photos/charlotte-nc/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/photos/charlotte-nc/</guid>
      <description>Charlotte&amp;rsquo;s got a lot of great things to do.
Cool things about Charlotte:  No zoo animals in captivity - they consent to paying rent 150,000 square foot NASCAR Hall of Fame gives way to easy streets Mint Museum in a banking city capital to see the origins of cash Underwhelming skyscrapers to let you enjoy the sunrise and sunset     View this post on Instagram        Lab on-the-go</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Times Square - New York City, NY</title>
      <link>/photos/new-york-usa/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/photos/new-york-usa/</guid>
      <description>Last Update: 2020-06-14 Times Square alone holds 1/6th of the hotel rooms available in NYC with 56% of businesses in the professional services space.
The few times I stayed in Times Square made me wonder just how much it required to keep the businesses afloat enough to pay rent and employees. Single room accommodations range from $1500 - $3000 USD / month. Commercial real estate rent is easily a factor of 20x generally and 100x in retail locations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Arizona, US</title>
      <link>/photos/cherrybeach-on/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/photos/cherrybeach-on/</guid>
      <description>The Grand Canyon is a steep-sided canyon carved by the Colorado River in Arizona, United States. The canyon is 277 miles (446 km) long, up to 18 miles (29 km) wide and attains a depth of over a mile (6,093 feet or 1,857 meters).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Birds of a Feather</title>
      <link>/photos/sr-71/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/photos/sr-71/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The world&amp;rsquo;s fastest airplane was also a pioneer in stealthiness. Note angled tails that greatly decreased radar profile. (Lockheed) SR-71 Blackbird streaking across continental U.S. (Lockheed) SR-71 Blackbird rolling down a highway en route to permanent display at the air museum at Robins Air Force Base in Georgia. (Jay Miller) &amp;hellip;&amp;quot;
&amp;quot;&amp;hellip;It was during the mid-1960s that the Blackbird, the SR-71, as the successor to the U-2 began bringing us intelligence information both photographic and electronic&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BY (Before Ye)</title>
      <link>/photos/ye/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/photos/ye/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chicago, US</title>
      <link>/photos/chicago-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/photos/chicago-us/</guid>
      <description>Officially the City of Chicago, is the most populous city in the U.S. state of Illinois, and the third-most-populous city in the United States. With an estimated population of 2,705,994 (2018), it is also the most populous city in the Midwestern United States. Chicago is the county seat of Cook County, the second-most-populous county in the US, with a small portion of the northwest side of the city extending into DuPage County near O&amp;rsquo;Hare Airport.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Miami Beach - Miami-Dade, FL</title>
      <link>/photos/miami-usa/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/photos/miami-usa/</guid>
      <description>The Grand Canyon is a steep-sided canyon carved by the Colorado River in Arizona, United States. The canyon is 277 miles (446 km) long, up to 18 miles (29 km) wide and attains a depth of over a mile (6,093 feet or 1,857 meters).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Placeholder</title>
      <link>/photos/ph/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/photos/ph/</guid>
      <description>3 Cheers for avoiding empty websites and including content placeholders.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scarborough Bluffs - Toronto, ON</title>
      <link>/photos/toronto-on-i/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/photos/toronto-on-i/</guid>
      <description>The Grand Canyon is a steep-sided canyon carved by the Colorado River in Arizona, United States. The canyon is 277 miles (446 km) long, up to 18 miles (29 km) wide and attains a depth of over a mile (6,093 feet or 1,857 meters).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chilean Empanadas</title>
      <link>/photos/grub-love-i/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/photos/grub-love-i/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>