<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>estebanvalencia.com</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on estebanvalencia.com</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2016 21:05:33 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Esteban Valencia</title>
      <link>/me/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2016 21:05:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/me/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to my site!
 I&amp;rsquo;m Esteban Valencia, a Canadian who likes to build digital and physical products to solve problems. You’ve now joined the many special people who have previously discovered my page. Congratulations!
I have always been interested in sharing my personal and professional experiences with others, so I decided to try archiving and collecting my findings into a blog. Since I graduated from the University of Western Ontario with a degree in Electrical Engineering, I started my career in consulting and data science aimed at driving profitability or reducing costs for businesses by boiling down complex ideas into actionable insights.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Terms and Privacy</title>
      <link>/privacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/privacy/</guid>
      <description>A notice for humans Hello fellow!
The person responsible for this website would like to let you know that this site does not collect nor store your personal information.
Occasionally, links to external sites may be what are colloquially known as affiliate links. This means that should you click on them and choose to make a purchase from the ensuing purveyor of goods, the owner of this site may receive compensation for bringing said purveyor to your attention.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>